in this tutorial I'll be going over how
在本教程中，我将介绍如何
you can use the transform tool in
您可以在中使用变换工具
inkscape I'll first be going over a
Inkscape我将首先复习一下
quick demonstration of what it is and
快速演示它是什么和
how it works and then I'll show you an
它是如何工作的，然后我将向你展示一个
example of how to create something
如何创造一些东西的例子
interesting with it like I've done here
很有趣，就像我在这里做的那样
with this spiraling hexagon design
这个螺旋形的六角形设计
before we get started though if you want
在我们开始之前，如果你想
to learn more about how inkscape Works
要详细了解Inkscape的工作原理，请执行以下操作
be sure to check out my inkscape master
一定要看看我的Inkscape大师
class it's a collection of over 80
班级它是一个超过80个人的集合
videos where we go over all of the tools
我们将在视频中查看所有工具
and features in inkscape and I explain
和Inkscape中的功能，我解释
what they are and demonstrate how they
它们是什么并演示它们如何
work kind of like how I'm doing in this
工作就像我在这里做的那样
video we even have a private Community
视频我们甚至有一个私人社区
where you can ask questions and get help
在这里您可以提出问题并获得帮助
from me anytime you want I'll have some
任何时候你想要我的，我都会有
information about that down below in the
关于这一点的信息，请参阅下面的
description if you want to check that
描述，如果您想要检查
out and with that out of the way let's
别挡道了，我们走吧
get started so I have this example
开始吧，所以我有这个例子
graphic placed on my document here and
在此处和我的文档上放置图形
I'm going to open up the transform menu
我要打开Transform菜单
by going to object and selecting
通过转到Object并选择
transform and it should open up over
转变，它应该开放超过
here on the right hand side of your
在你的右手边
screen now what the transform tool does
现在显示变换工具的作用
is it allows you to make basic
它是否允许您将基本的
transformations to objects that you
对您的对象进行变换
would normally make with the selection
通常会做出这样的选择
tool only it allows you to do it using
仅限工具它允许您使用
numerical values so if you come over
数值，所以如果你过来
here to the top you can see these tabs
在顶部，您可以看到这些选项卡
we have these different options for
我们有以下这些不同的选择
moving scaling rotating skewing and
移动、缩放、旋转倾斜和
Matrix we're going to ignore the Matrix
矩阵我们要忽略矩阵
one for this demonstration I'm just
一张是为了这个演示，我只是
going to show you how these other ones
我要向你们展示这些其他的
work so let's say I have this object on
工作，所以假设我戴着这个对象
my page and I want to move it over a
我的页面和我想把它移到
certain number of pixels you can
您可以使用一定数量的像素
normally move objects by just clicking
通常只需点击即可移动对象
and dragging but the problem with doing
拖拽，但这样做的问题是
it that way is that you don't get a
那样的话，你就不会得到
precise movement let's say I wanted to
准确的动作比方说我想要
move this over exactly 50 pixels I can
把这个正好移到50像素以上我可以
can come over here to the horizontal
可以从这里走到水平方向
input and type in 50 and then come down
输入并输入50，然后下来
here and click apply and you can see it
单击此处并单击应用，您可以看到它
moves the object over 50 pixels so let
将对象移动到50像素以上，以便让
me undo what I just did right there let
我解开我刚才做的事，让
me reset this value and now I'll show
我重置此值，现在我将显示
you how scale works scale is useful
你知道规模是如何运作的规模很有用
because normally when you want to scale
因为通常情况下，当您想要扩展
an object by a certain numerical value
按一定数值计算的对象
you would use the width and height
您将使用宽度和高度
inputs in the toolbar up top so if I
在顶部的工具栏中输入，因此如果我
wanted to scale this down to 400 pixels
我想把它缩小到400像素
wide I would type that in and press
我会把它打进去，然后按
enter and you can see it scales it down
进入，你可以看到它缩小了
but the the problem with using this
但是使用这个的问题是
approach is that it takes the object off
一种方法是，它将物体从
of the center of its axis so if you
它的轴心位置，所以如果你
notice the object is no longer in the
请注意，该对象不再位于
center of my document it now went to the
我的文档的中心现在转到了
top left because with these inputs up
左上角，因为当这些输入打开时
here it scales the object from the
在这里，它从
bottom right to the top left now if I
从右下角到左上角，如果我
undo that it'll put it back in the
解开它会把它放回
center the benefit of using the
集中了使用
transform tool is that it allows you to
转换工具是它允许您
scale the object using the numerical
使用数字缩放对象
value directly from the center and you
直接从中心获得价值，而您
can also use a percentage value as well
也可以使用百分比值
now if you want to use pixels you can go
现在，如果你想使用像素，你可以
ahead and select pixels but for this
在前面选择像素，但不是这样
demonstration I'll just use percentages
演示我将只使用百分比
and I'm just going to type in well first
我只想先打个好字
I'm going to select scale
我要选择比例
proportionately so it scales both
比例，因此它既可扩展，也可
dimensions and I'm going to scale this
维度，我将对此进行缩放
down by
向下
50% and I will click apply and you can
50%，我将单击应用，您可以
see what happens it scales the object
查看缩放对象时发生的情况
down exactly in the center so that it
恰好在中间，所以它
doesn't lose its alignment on the
不会失去它在
page now let's go over the rotate tab
现在，让我们来看看旋转选项卡
normally when you want to rotate an
通常情况下，当您想要旋转
object you can click on it to select it
对象，您可以单击它以将其选中
click on it again to get the rotation
再次点击即可获得旋转
handles and you can rotate it around
手柄，你可以旋转它
freeh hands like that or you can hold
弗雷这样的手，否则你可以握住
the control key and lock it to 15 degree
控制键并将其锁定到15度
increments the problem with using this
增加了使用此
approach is that you don't get an exact
方法是你不会得到一个确切的
rotation so let's say you wanted to
轮换，比方说你想
rotate your object by a specific
将您的对象旋转特定的
numerical value like 26° or some kind of
像26°这样的数值或某种
random number you would normally have to
随机数，你通常需要
click and drag like this and look
像这样点击并拖动，然后看
towards the bottom of the screen to see
在屏幕底部查看
the Angles and hope that you can release
《天使》，希望你能释放
the click exactly where you need it to
在您需要的位置点击
be or you can just use the rotation tool
BE或您可以使用旋转工具
so I can come over here and type in let
这样我就可以到这里来，输入LET
me just replace this value type in 26
我只需在26中替换此值类型
and you can choose whether to rotate it
您还可以选择是否旋转它
clockwise or counterclockwise and then
顺时针或逆时针，然后
click apply and you can see it rotated
单击应用，您可以看到它已旋转
the object 26° and the way the transform
物体26°和变换的方式
tool works is this is all cumulative so
工具的作用是所有这些都是累积的，所以
if I keep clicking apply over and over
如果我一遍又一遍地点击应用
again it'll rotate it
它会再次旋转它
26° relative to its previous position so
相对于其前一位置26°，因此
I can keep rotating this indefinitely
我可以无限期地轮换这个
like that and you get the
就像这样，你就会得到
idea now let's go over how you can
好了，现在让我们来了解一下如何
create that spiraling hexagon design
创造出螺旋形的六边形设计
that I showed you at the beginning of
我在一开始就向你们展示了
the video I'm going to grab my stars and
这个视频我要带着我的明星
polygons tool over here and the settings
此处的面工具和设置
I want to use are polygon I want six
我想用正多边形，我要六个
corners and rounded and randomize both
角和圆角，并随机化两者
set to zero and then I'm going to click
设置为零，然后我将单击
and drag on the canvas and then hold
在画布上拖动，然后按住
control and shift and click and drag so
Ctrl+Shift并单击并拖动
that we get a nice uh upright hexagon
我们得到了一个很好的，呃，直立的六边形
like that you can rotate it around to
就像这样，你可以旋转它来
make sure that the corners are going
确保弯道是顺畅的
perfectly up and down vertically like
垂直向上和向下完美地像
that and I'm going to grab my selection
然后我要拿出我的选择
tool and I first want to Center this on
Tool和我首先想要集中讨论这个
the page so I will come over here to
所以我会到这里来
object and I will choose a line
对象，我会选择一条线
distribute and I'm going to choose page
分发，我要选择页面
from the relative to dropdown and I'm
从相对到下拉列表，我是
going to Center this up on the page and
将这个放在页面的中央，然后
then I'm going to zoom in and I'm going
然后我要放大，然后我要
to hold control and shift and scale this
按住控制、Shift和Scaling
down to make it really small we want
让它变得非常小，我们想要的
this object to be pretty small and I'm
这个物体很小，而我
going to remove the fill color by
将通过以下方式删除填充颜色
clicking the Red X down here and I'm
点击下面的红色X，我就会
going to apply a black Stroke by holding
按住手势来应用黑色笔触
the shift key and pressing the color
Shift键并按下颜色
black next to that uh number right there
黑色的，就在那个呃数字旁边
or next to that red X and now I want to
或者在那个红色的X旁边，现在我想
make sure that this stroke is one pixel
确保此笔划为一个像素
so I'll open open up my fill and stroke
所以我会敞开心扉，敞开我的心扉
menu by double clicking this stroke box
通过双击此笔划框来选择菜单
down here and I'll come over here to the
在这下面，我会到这里来
stroke style Tab and I'm going to size
笔划样式选项卡和我要调整大小
this at one pixel and I want to make
这是一个像素，我想要制作
sure that the join has sharp corners and
确保连接处有尖锐的拐角和
then I want to come up here to this
然后我想来这里看看这个
setting in the toolbar that says when
工具栏中的设置，该设置指示何时
scaling objects scale the stroke width
缩放对象缩放笔触宽度
by the same proportion I want to make
按我想要的比例
sure that that is enabled and now what
确定该选项已启用，现在该怎么办？
I'm going to do is I'm going to come
我要做的就是我要来
over here to my transform tool and I'm
在这里我的变形工具，我是
going to use two different
我将使用两个不同的
Transformations I'm first going to scale
我首先要扩展的转型
it by 110% and then I'm going to rotate
110%，然后我要旋转
it by 10° but before I do that I want to
差了10度，但在此之前，我想
make a duplicate copy so this is the
复制一份，这样这就是
original copy I'm going to make a
原件我要制作一份
duplicate by either right clicking it
通过右击复制
and going to duplicate or just pressing
然后复制或直接按下
command D or controll D and when you
命令D或控制D，以及当您
press that you'll have a duplicate copy
按下你会有一份复印件
there and once you do that come over
在那里，一旦你做到了，就过来
here to the scale tab let's scale this
在这里，到Scale选项卡，让我们来缩放它
we'll first of all enable scale
我们将首先启用扩展
proportionately and we're going to scale
在比例上，我们将扩大规模
this by
这是由
110° or 110% and click apply and then
110度或110%，然后单击应用，然后
we'll come over here to rotate we're
我们会到这里来轮流我们是
going to rotate this by 10° so let me
我要把它旋转10度，让我
replate this replace this with 10 and
把这个换成10个，然后
there we go and now I'm just going to
我们走了，现在我要去
repeat that process over and over until
一遍又一遍重复这个过程，直到
we get the intended effect so I'm going
我们得到了预期的效果，所以我要去
to press command D again to duplicate
要再次按命令D以复制
the object and I will rotate it and then
物体和我会旋转它，然后
come over here and scale it and then I
到这里来，把它缩一下，然后我
will do that again press control D to
将再次执行此操作，按Ctrl D以
duplicate scale it and then rotate it
复制、缩放它，然后旋转它
and then do the same thing control D to
然后对控件D执行相同的操作
duplicate rotate it scale it and you can
复制旋转它，缩放它，你就可以
see that the design is starting to come
注意设计已经开始出现了
together as I do this so I'm going to
一起做这件事，所以我要
duplicate this a bunch of times and
把这个重复一遍，然后
apply these Transformations and then I
应用这些转换，然后我
will catch up with you when I'm all
我会追上你，当我
done and you can make as many copies as
完成后，您可以复制尽可能多的副本
you want I made this many right here if
你想让我在这里做这么多如果
I click and drag over all of these it'll
我点击并拖动所有这些，它将
show you how many objects you have
向你展示你有多少物品
selected let me move this out of the way
选中后，我可以将其移开
you can see we have 19 objects selected
您可以看到，我们选择了19个对象
so I have 19 copies in total what I'm
所以我总共有19份拷贝
going to do is I'm going to convert
我要做的是，我要把
these to a path so I'll go to path and
将这些放到一条路径上，所以我将转到路径和
select stroke to path and then I will
选择笔划到路径，然后我将
unify them together by going to path and
通过转到路径和路径将它们统一在一起
selecting Union and now what I will do
选择联合，现在我要做什么
is I will come back over here to my fill
我会回到这里尽情享受
and stroke tab I want to bring the
和笔划选项卡我想要带上
opacity down in half so I can see what
把不透明度降低一半，这样我就能看到
I'm about to do once I do this and now I
一旦我这样做了，我就会去做，而现在我
will go to path and select break apart
将转到路径并选择断开
and you can see what I mean there once
你可以在那里一次看到我的意思
you break that apart you can see all of
你把它拆开，你可以看到所有
the different layers beneath the
下面的不同层
original so I'll click off of that to
原创的，所以我将点击它来
deselect it and I want to take this
取消选择它，我想要这个
larger hexagon in the back here and just
后面有个更大的六角形
press delete on the keyboard to get rid
按键盘上的Delete键可以删除
of that and then I'll take this object
然后我就拿这个东西
in the center and press delete to get
在中间并按Delete以获取
press delete to get rid of that and then
按Delete将其删除，然后
I will bring the opacity of this up to
我将把这件事的不透明性提高到
to 100% And if you want you can go and
到100%，如果你愿意，你可以去
color in each of these arms a different
每只手臂上的颜色都不同
color if you want to apply your own
如果您想要应用您自己的颜色
design uh your own style to it or what
为它设计呃你自己的风格还是什么的
you could do is you could just select it
您所能做的就是选择它
all and go to path and select Union and
全部并转到路径，然后选择联合和
we end up with this cool little abstract
我们最终得到了这个很酷的小抽象
sort of hexagon shape so I think that
一种六角形，所以我认为
should do it for this tutorial that's
在本教程中应该这样做，即
just one example of how you can use the
这只是一个如何使用
transform tool in inkscape to create an
在inkscape中转换工具以创建
interesting design if you found this
如果你发现了这个，有趣的设计
lesson useful then consider checking out
课程有用，然后考虑查看
my inkscape master class it's a
我的水墨风景大师班是一堂
collection of over 60 videos where I go
收集了我去过的60多个视频
over all of the tools and features in
中的所有工具和功能
inkscape and I explain what they are and
inkscape和我解释了它们是什么，
demonstrate how they work kind of like
演示它们的工作原理有点像
how I did in this video we even have a
我在这个视频中的表现我们甚至有一个
private Community where you can ask
私人社区，您可以询问
questions and get help from me anytime
随时向我提问并寻求帮助
you want and best of all there's no
你想要的，最重要的是没有
monthly membership fees you just pay $17
每月会员费只需支付17美元
one time and you're in for Life I'll
一次，你就会终身监禁我会
have some information about that down
有一些相关信息
below if you want to check that out as
如果您想检查一下，请在下面作为
always thanks for watching
始终感谢观看
oh
哦
[Music]
[音乐]